B1.
Toby, the exchange student, will go back to the USA soon.
David and Nora are planning a goodbye party for him.
Listen to their plan and complete Nora's notes below.
Toby is going back to the USA next week.
Shall we have a goodbye party for him?
That's a good idea.
When shall we have the party?
How about this Saturday?
That's the 12th of May.
Saturday the 12th of May. OK.
Shall we meet at 6pm? That's fine.
But where can we have the party?
What about the Star Hotel? Oh no.
It's too expensive.
How about the school hall?
That sounds great.
I can ask for Miss Law's help.
I hope the school allows us to use it. Me too.
Now who shall we invite to the party?
Everyone from our class, of course.
But Toby also has some friends in other classes.
Let's invite them too. OK.
Let's talk about the details later after school.